

# Nikolai Kuzmich Backend developer

▶ Phone: +375 (33) 640-04-64

■ Email: nikorde@gmail.com

### About

#### I'm Nikolai Kuzmich.

Currently, I'm working as a developer at the transport company. My last project is a desktop ERP system for cargo transportation. I'm looking for a job with a modern technology stack now. Technologies are my passion, and I want to be a part of professional development and self-education. I'm open to a new experience and ready for new challenges! Are you ready to rock

Age : 32 years old

Languages: Russian, English

Location : Brest, Belarus

**Interest**: Football, Photoshop,

Video editing

#### **Education & Skills**



#### **Education**

2006-2008
 Brest State Technical University
 Automation of Technological
 Processes and Production

2010-2015 Brest State Technical University Technical operation of vehicles



## **Experience**

2010-2018YURIDAN LTDLogistician

2018-2020 YURIDAN LTD Software Developer

Devealopment desktop ERP system. Delphi, PostgreSQL Integration with GPS tracking system and other web services HTML & CSS 40%

JAVASCRIPT 50%

SQL 85%

DELPHI 90%







